# Evandro Carreira

## Web Developer, Graphics Engineer

evandro.carreira@gmail.com

+55 (48) 98454-3845

Evandro Carreira has been working with the development of web technologies and geoprocessing for 10 years, always focusing on innovation and advancement in this constantly growing area. Graduated in Computer Science from UNESP, he believes that information is a modern collective good and should be available to all. He currently focuses his research on space technologies and visual processing, using math concepts as tools to understand and handle data.

#### Education

# Bachelor Degree in Computer Science

UNESP - Universidade Estadual Paulista

2010 a 2015

## **Recent Experiences**

#### **Grupo Tesseract**

Web Development

Fullstack Web Developer

2016 - Now

### Instituto Soma

Geopraphic Informations Systems

Software Engineer, Databender

2016 - 2018

#### **Brisarte**

Videomapping & Interactive Projections

Graphics Engineer e VFX

2016 - Now

#### Vivalá

Tourism and volunteer platform

Web Developer e Robopsychologist

2015 - 2017

#### Skills

- Web Development
- Geoprocessing
- Design Patterns
- Computer Graphics
- Computational Geometry
- Regular expressions
- GPU Programming
- Data modeling

#### **Tools**



### Languages

Portuguese Native

English Intermediate

German Basic